<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fin Sim App</string>
    <string name="halle_intro">HALLE </string>
    <string name="halle_bio">Age: 20 \nOccupation: Work Study at the University of Pennsylvania \nLocation: Philadelphia, PA \nRelationship Status: Single \nYearly Income: $4500 \nYou use public transportation to travel the city and are not a part of any relationships currently. You run every morning and maintain a healthy life-style. As a student, the largest issues you face are paying off your student debt and budgeting your money between food, housing, and fun. You have a work-study job where you make $8.15 an hour.</string>
    <string name="jiamin_intro">JIAMIN </string>
    <string name="jiamin_bio"> Age: 35 \nOccupation: Werizon Sales Representative \nLocation: Columbus, Ohio. \nRelationship Status: Single \nYearly Income: $45,000 \nYour annual income is comfortable for a single woman with no kids, but not generous enough to afford vacations. In fact, you haven’t left the country for over a decade. You commute for 75 minutes every day to work in an old but reliable junker Honda Civic ‘95. You are seeking a relationship but as you grow older, you realize how much more difficult it is to make new friends and how easy it is to drift apart from old friends. You worry that your prime years have passed by.  </string>
    <string name="lauren_intro"> LAUREN </string>
    <string name="lauren_bio">Age: 42 \nOccupation: Investment banker \nLocation: NYC. \nRelationship Status: Married \nYearly Income: $250,000 \nYou have three children, and own a car, boat, and vacation home. The biggest issue you face is that you have a very busy lifestyle and often lack social time with your family and friends. </string>
    <string name="swetha_intro">SWETHA </string>
    <string name="swetha_bio">Age: 75 \nOccupation: Retired for 12 years \nLocation: Fort Myers, Florida \nRelationship Status: Married \nYearly Income: $0 \nYou have two grandchildren whom you love very much. You suffer from arthritis and cataracts, finding yourself restricted to the confines of your home more and more frequently as time passes. You have found that the lifestyle you have become accustomed to and your frequent health issues have led to your retirement fund depleting faster than you planned, which makes the future uncertain.</string>
    <string name="halle_story_0">Your friends text you to go out the night before the exam. Do you...</string>
    <string name="halle_choice_0_0">Stay in and keep studying to make sure you ace the exam.</string>
    <string name="halle_choice_0_1">Go out to the bars and have a fun time with your friends to de-stress.</string>
    <string name="halle_choice_0_2">Compromise for a quick dinner out together.</string>
    <string name="jiamin_story_0">Because you are dissatisfied, you decide it’s time for a change. Do you...</string>
    <string name="jiamin_choice_0_0">start searching for new jobs - costs $0 but risks your stable $45,000 salary</string>
    <string name="jiamin_choice_0_1">travel abroad - costs $1,500</string>
    <string name="jiamin_choice_0_2">go to Single’s Night at the Bar every Friday - Costs $30 every time</string>
    <string name="lauren_story_0">One of your children fell and broke his arm. Do you...</string>
    <string name="lauren_choice_0_0">Take him to the hospital - with insurance, this will cost you $900</string>
    <string name="lauren_choice_0_1">Make a makeshift cast at home - costs $10</string>
    <string name="lauren_choice_0_2">Comfort him and hope it heals with time - costs $0</string>
    <string name="swetha_story_0">You want to take your grandchild out for her birthday but she wants to go to the mall. Do you...</string>
    <string name="swetha_choice_0_0">Take her out and risk injury and fatigue - injury would cost $150</string>
    <string name="swetha_choice_0_1">Suggest something less fun to do inside your house such as bake - Costs $15</string>
    <string name="swetha_choice_0_2">Send her a card with money in it so she can buy whatever she wants - Costs $25</string>
    <string name="halle_story_1">Your three figure student debt is accumulating. Do you...</string>
    <string name="halle_choice_1_0">Give up 10% of your paycheck every week to start paying it off the interest now - Costs $15 of your $160 weekly paycheck</string>
    <string name="halle_choice_1_1">Wait until you make a starting salary of $75,000 a year to pay off your debt after college -$0 right now, but will add up later on</string>
    <string name="halle_choice_1_2">Put it off until later and have your parents help you out</string>
    <string name="jiamin_story_1">You try your hand at kids, you babysit your nephew. Do you...</string>
    <string name="jiamin_choice_1_0">Find raising kids too difficult and that it is not the lifestyle for you- Costs $0
</string>
    <string name="jiamin_choice_1_1">Have a great time and realize you want to find someone to settle down with more than ever- Costs $30,000 for a wedding you will save for for 2 years with your partner</string>
    <string name="jiamin_choice_1_2">Realize you want to have a kid now and don’t have time to meet the right person - Costs $5,000 to adopt</string>
    <string name="lauren_story_1">You are offered a promotion at work that will increase your salary, but also increase the amount of time spent at work. Do you...</string>
    <string name="lauren_choice_1_0">Take the job and the bonus that comes will it</string>
    <string name="lauren_choice_1_1">Negotiate the offer to attain the higher position, but give up the bonus to have a more balanced schedule</string>
    <string name="lauren_choice_1_2">Reject the offer</string>
    <string name="swetha_story_1">Your country club is hosting a Karaoke night that is out of your comfort zone but the winner gets a $50 gift card. Do you...</string>
    <string name="swetha_choice_1_0">Not take the competition seriously as you have a fun time and are busy meeting new people </string>
    <string name="swetha_choice_1_1">Take the competition seriously and win the competition </string>
    <string name="swetha_choice_1_2">Stay home because socializing is difficult </string>
    <string name="halle_story_2">Your scholarship requires a 3.4 GPA and a clean record. Do you...</string>
    <string name="halle_choice_2_0">Say no to going out to parties to ensure you never get caught and lose your scholarship - Costs $0</string>
    <string name="halle_choice_2_1"> Lose track of time at the gym with your friends and forget to do homework - Costs $0
</string>
    <string name="halle_choice_2_2">Find a balance between your academic and social life- physically taxing to keep up with</string>
    <string name="jiamin_story_2">You decide to look into buying a stock in Werizon. Do you...</string>
    <string name="jiamin_choice_2_0">Take classes about the stock market to prepare your investments - Costs $600 for the class but you can make a profit of $1,000</string>
    <string name="jiamin_choice_2_1">Roll the dice and buy 3 shares at $60 each - Costs $180 but may profit</string>
<string name="jiamin_choice_2_2">Do not invest any money in stocks</string>
<string name="lauren_story_2">Your friends want to go out for the night, but you have to work. Do you...</string>
<string name="lauren_choice_2_0">Call in sick and take some much needed personal time</string>
<string name="lauren_choice_2_1">Cancel on your friends and work</string>
<string name="lauren_choice_2_2">Quit your job</string>
<string name="swetha_story_2">A nigerian prince emails you asking for financial assistance. Do you...</string>
<string name="swetha_choice_2_0">Send him the money, I mean he is a Nigerian prince.</string>
<string name="swetha_choice_2_1">Take the competition seriously and win the competition </string>
<string name="swetha_choice_2_2">Stay home because socializing is difficult </string>
</resources>